A Guide to the Holmes Run Acres Civic Association Collection, 1951-2021
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 9: Directories, 1954-2021
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2012 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2015 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2016 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2017 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2018 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2019 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2020 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2020-2021 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Series 10: Clippings and Articles, 1951-2020
  - Clipping - Advertisement - “Only 10 left... Holmes Run”, Undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Clipping - Advertisement - “As new as tomorrow!, Undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - HRA related articles and newspaper clippings (1 of 3), 1951-2020 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - HRA related articles and newspaper clippings (2 of 3), 1951-2020 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - HRA related articles and newspaper clippings (3 of 3), 1951-2020 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - HRA related articles and newspaper clippings (1 of 3), 1951-2000 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - HRA related articles and newspaper clippings (2 of 3), 1951-2000 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - HRA related articles and newspaper clippings (3 of 3), 1951-2000 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Series 11: Oversize Materials, 1951-2011
  - HRA - The Early Years - Photos on Posterboard, photos by Florence Strickler [MOVED FROM SUB-SERIES 4-2: PHOTOGRAPHS - HRA 10TH ANNIVERSARY, 1961], 1961 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - “American Revolution Bicentennial Certificate of Appreciation to HRA, 1976 [MOVED FROM SUB-SERIES 3-1: ANNIVERSARIES - HRA 25TH ANNIVERSARY, 1976], 1976 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Sarah Lahr features on HRA in the Sun Echo newspaper, 1950s [NOTE: In poor physical shape, acidic paper used.] [MOVED FROM SUB-SERIES 4-1: SCRAPBOOKS], 1950s (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - HRA Scrapbook - Compiled by Florence Strickler (Florence was the first historian for HRA) for the 10th Anniversary of HRA, 1961 [NOTE: In poor physical shape, acidic paper used.] [MOVED FROM SUB-SERIES 4-1: SCRAPBOOKS], 1961 (Box 24)
  - Architectural drawings - Luria (1950-1952), Gaddy (1954), and Bodor (1958) models, 1951-1958
  - Architectural drawings - 3319 Hemlock Dr. (formerly known as 2409 Hemlock Dr., house numbers changed in 1955) - 8 drawings, 1965-1966
  - Poster board - HRACA 50th Anniversary Gala - Fairview Park Marriott, 2001 October 6
  - Poster board - HRACA 50th Anniversary - Ice cream socials, block parties, house tour, day in the park, 50-year residents, park spruce up day, 2001
  - Poster board - HRACA 50th Anniversary - Garden tour and creative arts festival, 2001
  - Poster board - Holmes Run Acres (1951) and Pine Springs (1952) - Chris Martin, c. 2001
  - Poster board - Open Holmes - Sign-up, c. 2014
  - Commonwealth of Virginia General Assembly - House Resolution No. 502 - Commending the Holmes Run Acres Civic Association, April 11, 2011 - Presented to HRACA in honor of the 60th Anniversary of HRA [Framed], 2011